{
    "subject": "resource/Edgar_Rice_Burroughs",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Edgar Rice Burroughs",
    "human_readable": "The label of Edgar Rice Burroughs is Edgar Rice Burroughs.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9722058176994324,
            "question": "Who is Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9266873002052307,
            "question": "What is the full name of Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9029111266136169,
            "question": "What genre is Edgar Rice Burroughs known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.872955858707428,
            "question": "Are there any famous characters associated with Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8581882119178772,
            "question": "Is there any other information known about Edgar Rice Burroughs besides his name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8308581113815308,
            "question": "What kind of works did Edgar Rice Burroughs create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7644332647323608,
            "question": "When was Edgar Rice Burroughs born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7490492463111877,
            "question": "Was Edgar Rice Burroughs recognized for his writing during his lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7450026869773865,
            "question": "Where did Edgar Rice Burroughs live and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6798320412635803,
            "question": "How has Edgar Rice Burroughs's work influenced popular culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Edgar Rice Burroughs is Edgar Rice Burroughs.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7894_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Edgar Rice Burroughs live and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7894_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Edgar Rice Burroughs recognized for his writing during his lifetime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7894_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Edgar Rice Burroughs born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7894_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7894_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7894_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7894_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7894_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7894_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7894_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7894_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7894_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7894_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7894_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n**Triple:** Edgar Rice Burroughs born in Chicago.\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. All five documents mention that Edgar Rice Burroughs was born in 1875, and one document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7894/re-ranker-msmarco/75.txt) specifically mentions that he was born in Chicago.\n\nSo, the answer is:\n\n`{ \"output\": \"yes\" }`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The label of Edgar Rice Burroughs is Edgar Rice Burroughs\" is correct according to the provided documents, as each document uses his full name consistently."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}